Art Collins Papers ARC.0001
Library and Archives
- Series I: Iggy Pop [RESTRICTED], 1985-2005, undated
  - Virgin America delivery extension, 2002 September 9 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Solo offers [RESTRICTED], 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 15-16)
  - Virgin Records statement, January-June, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Royalty statements, 1988-1991 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Royalties, July-December, 1987-1992, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 19-20)
  - Reed, Lou, video "Ecstasy" (Michele Civetta, director), 2000 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Royalties Virgin Records, July-December, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - South by Southwest video, 2000 January 11 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Cleopatra Records / Bug Music, 1999 October 13 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - "Lust For Life," SFR phones, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Montreal Jazz Festival, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - "Corruption," Bug Music, 2000 January 11 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - "Shaking All Over" and "Cold Metal," ESPN, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - "Passenger," Best Pub Jukebox Anthems... Ever, 2000 April 4 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - "Lust For Life," Classic Love Songs in Hollywood, 2000 April 19 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - "Lust For Life," IKEA CD, Sweden, 2000 April 19 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - "Passenger," Big Spike, 2000 April 18 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - "Lust For Life," Next Weekend's Party Album, 2000 April 18 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - "Candy," FM Radio Anthems, 2000 April 19 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - "Lust For Life," Cigarettes and Alcohol, 2000 May 12 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Buddah Records re-release, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - "Louie, Louie," Lock Stock TV Soundtrack, 2000 May 12 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - "Lust For Life," Ralph's Best Ever Songs For the Weekend, 2000 May 2 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - "China Girl," Real World, 2000 April 28 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - "Lust For Life," Ryan Caulfield, 2000 April 11 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - "Johanna," Recycler film, 2000 April 28 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - "Passenger," Limozeno, 2000 April 26 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Strictly Sinatra, 2000 May 1 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - "Fucking Alone," "Best Attitude Songs", 2000 March 1 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - "Real Wild Child," Rock Collection, 2000 March 1 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - "Passenger," Dommelsch Beer, 2000 March 3 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - "Passenger," Champions of Rock, 2000 March 6 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - "Lust For Life," Shockwave, 2000 March (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Poetry booklet Welcome to the Voice, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - "Lust For Life," corporate video, 2000 December (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - "Nightclubbing," Nash Bridges, 2000 December (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - "Lust For Life," All Time Greatest Movie Songs, 2001 January 2 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - "I Need Somebody," Queer As Folk, 2000 November 22 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - "Passenger," New World Disorder, 2000 December (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - VH1 The List, "Search and Destroy", 2000 December 2 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Versace, Milan, 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Save the Last Dance film, heir letters, 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - "Candy," Classic Rock 13, 2000 November 28 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - "I'll Be Seeing You," Lover, Korea, 2000 November 20 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - "Candy," Double Shot of Rock ANZ comp, 2000 November 20 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - "Passenger," When Brenda Met Trudie, 2000 November 27 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Leibovitz, Anne, pix, GQ (Germany), 2000 November 10 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Bug Music statement, April-June, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Sessions At West 54th, Bug Music letter, 2000 September 7 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Leo Cara's party, 2000 August 8 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Rolling Stone photo competition, German, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - William Morris, demo, Tim Curtis, 2000 July 20 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - "Passenger," New World Disorder, 2000 August 25 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - "I Need Somebody," KFC, UK and Erie, 2000 September 6 (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - VH1 "100 Greatest LPs" 100 Greatest Albums of Rock and Roll, "Raw Power," Bug Music, 2000 August 24 (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - "In the Deathcar," Hong Kong (Bug Music), 2000 August (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - "Bad Boyz," (HBO) IFC channel, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - "Passenger," Panrico bread, 2000 August 21 (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - "Passenger," "Corruption," Pizza Hut, Australia, 2000 August (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - "Passenger," Golden Age of Rock, Germany, Universal, 2000 August 14 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - "Real Wild Child," Rock Giants CD, Universal, Germany, 2000 August (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - "Passenger," Adventures of Sebastian Coe, 2000 August 10 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Spin Cycle, "Dirt," "I Got a Right," Bug Music, 2000 August 4 (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - "Lust For Life," Royal Caribbean, 8/2000 time buy, 2000 August 8 (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - "I'll Be Seeing You," Jazz on Cinema, Vol. 2, Virgin, 2000 July 27 (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - "Lust For Life," Ever Get the Feeling You've Been Cheated: The 70's Punk Rebellion, Rhino / Virgin, 2000 July 18 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - "Lust For Life," Off the Top CD, OSNY Music, Australia, 2000 July 27 (Box 8, Folder 82)
  - "Penetration," Intimacy, 2000 July 31 (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - "Lust For Life," Tucker (NBC), Bug Music, 2000 June 28 (Box 8, Folder 84)
  - "Nightclubbing," Modern Rock, Time-Life, 2000 October 13 (Box 8, Folder 85)
  - Adami, French money, 2000 August 28 (Box 8, Folder 86)
  - "Real Wild Child," Biker Jens, Norway, 2000 September 6 (Box 8, Folder 87)
  - "Passenger," Robbie Williams DVD, 2000 August 29 (Box 8, Folder 88)
  - "I Need Somebody," Queer As Folk, 2000 October (Box 8, Folder 89)
  - "Search and Destroy," VH1 The List "Best Pump Up Song", 2000 October 25 (Box 8, Folder 90)
  - "Passenger," Jaguar cars, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 91)
  - "Facade," Angel Eyes movie, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 92)
  - "Raw Power," VH1 Legends: The Pretenders, 2000 October 19 (Box 8, Folder 93)
  - "Search and Destroy," Shannon's Deal, NBC, 2000 October (Box 8, Folder 94)
  - "Real Wild Child," On the Road compilation, Sweden, 2000 October 19 (Box 8, Folder 95)
  - "Nightclubbing," "Bad Boyz," The Source: Sound Lab, 2000 October (Box 8, Folder 96)
  - "Aiesha," Evening Standard ad, London, 2000 September 29 (Box 8, Folder 97)
  - "Search and Destroy," Behind the Music: Go-Go's, 2000 September 29 (Box 8, Folder 98)
  - "Monster Men," Stupid Invaders game, decline, 2000 September 12 (Box 8, Folder 99)
  - "Search and Destroy," Almost Famous movie, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 100)
  - Raw Power songs, VH1's 100 Greatest Albums of Rock and Roll, 2000 October 19 (Box 8, Folder 101)
  - "Passenger," Guinness commercial, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 102)
  - "Life For Life," Behind the Music: 3rd Anniversary, 2000 September 26 (Box 8, Folder 103)
  - "Nightclubbing," Save the Last Dance, 2000 October 17 (Box 8, Folder 104)
  - "Shake Appeal," VH1 The List, 2000 September 14 (Box 8, Folder 105)
  - Rhino punk box set Ever Get the Feeling You've Been Cheated: The 70s Punk Rebellion, 2000 August 4 (Box 8, Folder 106)
  - "Lust For Life," Donna's Top 200 Aller Tijden, Volume 3, 2000 September 21 (Box 8, Folder 107)
  - "Gimme Danger," Dogtown, 2000 September 15 (Box 8, Folder 108)
  - Iggy poem, "Fleas", 2000 September 19 (Box 8, Folder 109)
  - Excite, UK TV spot - No, 2000 October 18 (Box 8, Folder 110)
  - Crow documentary, 2000 September 29 (Box 8, Folder 111)
  - Stereo Vision LA, Iggy paintings, 2000 October 18 (Box 8, Folder 112)
  - "Search and Destroy," Red Hot Chili Peppers DVD, 2000 October 6 (Box 8, Folder 113)
  - "China Girl," VH1 Storytellers, 2000 October 6 (Box 8, Folder 114)
  - Bug (Music) statements, 1-7, 2000 (and song licensing), 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 115)
  - Bug Music statements, 7-12, 2000 (and song licensing), 1998, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 1, Box 8, Folder 116)
  - Licensing and touring, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - "Real Wild Child," VH1 / Best Buy, 2000 January 24 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Death in Vegas, Gran Turismo 2000, 2000 August 8 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - "Lust For Life," Modern Rock, Vol. 18, 2000 June 16 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - "Lust For Life," Ally McBeal, 2001 February 15 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - "Dirt" / "Down on the Street," Spin Cycle movie, 1997, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - "Passenger," Adventures of Sebastian Coe, 2000 February 25 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Arista Heritage Series, Best of:, 2000 March 2 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - KLM magazine request, 2000 March (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - "Passenger," Freaks and Geeks, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - "Passenger," Doctor Martens Box Set, 2000 January 26 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - "I'll Be Seeing You," EMI Korea, 2000 February 10 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - "Lust For Life," VH1 Behind the Music: 1977, 2000 February (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - "Avenue B," 20th Century Lullabies, 2000 February 8 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - "Candy," Picking Up the Pieces, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - "Lust For Life," Pottpett Rock 2 (Iceland), 2000 February 1 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - "Nightclubbing," Shyne sample, 2000 January (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - "Lust For Life," Ryan Caulfield TV, 2000 January 20 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - "Avenue B," Belgium compilation, 2000 November 2 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - "Lust For Life," Best Student Anthems, South Africa, 2000 November 10 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Reebok advertisement, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Alfa Romeo, EMI Publishing "Lust For Life", 2000 January 14 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - "I'll Be Seeing You," Now That's Vocal, Australia Virgin, 2000 January 19 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - "Louie, Louie," Motorock, 2000 January 19 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Funhouse box set, 2000 February 25 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - "Tonight," Behind the Music: Tina Turner, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - du Poniface, Marc, Space Goofs, "Passenger," Saturn copyright infringement, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Dogtown, "Gimme Danger", 2001 January 23 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - "Lust For Life," WBTV, Nikki, 2001 February 2 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - "Search and Destroy," VH1 100 Most Shocking Moments in Rock and Roll, 2001 January 11 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - "Down on the Street," Knockaround Guys, 2001 January (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - "Passenger," Rock Party, GSA, 2001 January 26 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Les Enfants du Rock, "Lust For Life", 2001 January 31 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Nude and Rude and Lust For Life two pack, Virgin Europe, 2000 June 22 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - "Lust For Life," The Replacements movie, 2000 March (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - "Passenger," British Airways, 2000 March 29 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - "Wild America," Platinum Rock - The 90s, 2000 June 19 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - "Passenger," Club Makeup, 2000 June 15 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - "Lust For Life," Modern Rock, Vol. 18 - Loud and Raw, 2000 June 16 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Stein, Mandy, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - "Penetration," promo synch (Bug Music), 2000 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - "Undefeated," Belgium CD, Klass X (Virgin), 2000 April 3 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - "Lust For Life," Shockwave Corp. VID, 2000 March 28 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Le Serpent a Plumes, "I Need More", 2000 April (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - '99 Tour, 2000 finals, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Casino, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 46-47)
  - Rose, Dan, circa 2000 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Reebok ad prototype, 2000 June 20 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Dell Computer sessions, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Saviola, Jerry, Grey Advertising, 2000 November 30 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - MVO Ltd., 2000 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Roth, Alan, Florida guy, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - McGregor, Tim, 2000 February 16 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Escape From Hollywood, "Lust For Life", 2000 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Goodyear ad script, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Death in Vegas, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - "Hollywood Affair," Hollywood Goes Wild, 2000 February 14 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - "Girls of New York," Cacharel fragrances, 2000 February 16 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - "Penetration," Intimacy movie, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - "Lust For Life," Sugar and Spice film, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Doors project, Elektra contract, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - "Lust For Life," Radio Rock, Vol. 1, France, Morocco, etc., 2000 June 19 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Virgin Germany, Millenia Nova (and Kieran McGee copyright claim), 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 64-65)
  - Solo Summer gigs, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 66-68)
  - Call sheets, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 69-70)
  - Gelman contract (and song licensing), 2004-2005 (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - Financials, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 72-73)
  - "Lust For Life," Rock and Cinema, EMI France, 2005 March (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - "Passenger," Halvliter Rock, Norway, 2005 March 23 (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - "Some Weird Sin," New Blood, (Bug Music), 2005 (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - "Passenger," 30 Days (documentary), 2005 March 21 (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - "Dirt," House of Wax (Bug Music), 2005 (Box 9, Folder 78)
  - "Dog Food," "Five Foot One," Tomorrow Show, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 79)
  - "Passenger," Volvo Museum, 2005 February 24 (Box 9, Folder 80)
  - "Little Know It All," The Right Stuff, 2005 February 24 (Box 9, Folder 81)
  - "Butt Town," Fresh Prince of Bel Air, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 82)
  - "Little Know It All," Comp'd, 2005 February 14 (Box 9, Folder 83)
  - "Passenger," The Insider ( Entertainment Tonight Oscar salute), 2005 February (Box 9, Folder 84)
  - "Success," Lords of Dogtown, 2005 February (Box 9, Folder 85)
  - "Passenger," Chevrolet (no go), 2005 February 9 (Box 9, Folder 86)
  - "Lust For Life," The Moguls, 2005 February (Box 9, Folder 87)
  - "Success," I Love the 90s VH1, 2005 February 17 (Box 9, Folder 88)
  - "I Wanna Be Your Dog," Coachella DVD, 2005 March 28 (Box 9, Folder 89)
  - "Lust For Life," Guitar Hero video game, 2005 March 30 (Box 9, Folder 90)
  - "Lust For Life," 1977 - The Great Funk Hits, EMI Japan, 2005 April 1 (Box 9, Folder 91)
  - "Beside You," Skate More video/DVD, 2005 April 6 (Box 9, Folder 92)
  - "Some Weird Sin," New Blood video/DVD, 2005 April 6 (Box 9, Folder 93)
  - "Boogie Boy," Crossing Jordan, NBC series, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 94)
  - "Passenger," The Weatherman, Bug Music, 2005 March 29 (Box 9, Folder 95)
  - Family Stone, Iggy poster, 2005 February 4 (Box 9, Folder 96)
  - BBC Worldwide statements, 2004 December 14 (Box 9, Folder 97)
  - "Passenger," Freaky Styley, 2005 February 7 (Box 9, Folder 98)
  - Royal Caribbean, December 2004 - "Lust For Life", 2005 February 1 (Box 9, Folder 99)
  - "Little Electric Chair," Viva La Bam (MTV), 2004-2005 (Box 9, Folder 100)
  - CD Box, '70s Stooges, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 101)
  - Underground Garage lineup, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 102)
  - "Bang Bang," Baker Video, 2004 December 9 (Box 9, Folder 103)
  - Allaire Studios, 2004 August 17 (Box 9, Folder 104)
  - "Lust For Life," Cold Case, 2004 December (Box 9, Folder 105)
  - Music video distribution 2005, 2004 December 21 (Box 9, Folder 106)
  - Brothers of the Head, 4 songs, Bug Music, 2004 December 14 (Box 9, Folder 107)
  - "Candy," German film, 2004 December 17 (Box 9, Folder 108)
  - "Lust For Life," EMI Portugal, wine advertisement, 2004 December 17 (Box 9, Folder 109)
  - "Passenger," Juniper Bank, 2004 December 22 (Box 9, Folder 110)
  - Punk! DVD, Bug Music, 2 songs, 2004 December 8 (Box 9, Folder 111)
  - "Passenger," Weatherman, 2004-2005 (Box 9, Folder 112)
  - "Lust For Life," Dr. Vegas, 2004 October 21 (Box 9, Folder 113)
  - "Whatever," Rock Energy II (Greece), 2004 October 6 (Box 9, Folder 114)
  - "Passenger," This is TV Commercial, EMI Hungary, 2004 October 14 (Box 9, Folder 115)
  - "Candy," Rabenkinder TV film, Germany, 2004 October 19 (Box 9, Folder 116)
  - "Lust For Life," Royal Caribbean / "I Wanna Be Your Dog," Friday Night Lights, 2004 October 1 (Box 9, Folder 117)
  - "Passenger," 30 Days, NBC TV, 2004 October 22 (Box 9, Folder 118)
  - "I Wanna Be Your Dog," XXX documentary, 2004 October 4 (Box 9, Folder 119)
  - "Lust For Life," World's Greatest Artists, 2004 October 6 (Box 9, Folder 120)
  - "[Real] Wild Child," Friday's Rock N' Roll, Philippines, 2004 October (Box 9, Folder 121)
  - Copyright renewals 1977, Bug Music, 2004 November 19 (Box 9, Folder 122)
  - "Candy," Nineties Complete, 2005 January 19 (Box 9, Folder 123)
  - "Passenger," Nachtschidcht, Volume 16, Austria, 2005 January 21 (Box 9, Folder 124)
  - "Candy," Showtime 10, Hungary, 2005 January 19 (Box 9, Folder 125)
  - "Search and Destroy," Brothers of the Head, 2005 January 26 (Box 9, Folder 126)
  - MVO, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 127)
  - Grumble 2003, 2003-2004 (Box 9, Folder 128)
  - MVO Summer 2003 (Box 9, Folder 129)
  - "Lust For Life," Drive compilation, 2001 December 19 (Box 9, Folder 130)
  - "Funtime," VH1's Greatest TV Moments, 2001 December 19 (Box 9, Folder 131)
  - "I Wanna Be Your Dog," Dogtown movie, 2001 December 11 (Box 9, Folder 132)
  - August Euro wrap-up 10-1-2001 (Box 9, Folder 133)
  - Pinsard, Tibo, Stooges documentary, France, 2001 September 4 (Box 9, Folder 134)
  - "Most important TV moments" (UK), 2001 September 2 (Box 9, Folder 135)
  - VH1 History of Music and Sexuality, 2001 March 22 (Box 9, Folder 136)
  - "Nightclubbing," Shyne Blaze Battle, 2001 May (Box 9, Folder 137)
  - "China Girl," VH1 Storytellers, 2001 May 30 (Box 9, Folder 138)
  - "Lust For Life," MTV True Live: I'm a Private Wrestler, 2001 May 25 (Box 9, Folder 139)
  - "Passenger," Waking Life film Virgin / Bug Music, 2001 June 28 (Box 9, Folder 140)
  - "Search and Destroy," 100 Most Shocking Moments in Rock and Roll, 2001 July 3 (Box 9, Folder 141)
  - "Raw Power" / "Shake Appeal," All Access: 25 Years of Punk, 2001 July 5 (Box 9, Folder 142)
  - "Nightclubbing," All Access: 25 Years of Punk, 2001 July 5 (Box 9, Folder 143)
  - "Lust For Life," Nikki TV show, Bug Music, 2001 June 6 (Box 9, Folder 144)
  - "Lust For Life," World's Best Beer Songs, Australia and New Zealand, 2001 September 13 (Box 9, Folder 145)
  - "Passenger," Guitar Club Classics, 2001 September 31 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - "Passenger," French Fried Music, film producers, 2001 August 2001 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - "Passenger," Complete History of Punk, 4 CD box set, 2001 August 9 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - "Lust For Life," Loaded: Very Best in 90s Indie, 2001 August 6 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - "Lust For Life," Best Sporting Anthems...Ever, South Africa, 2001 August 6 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - "I Need Somebody," Queer As Folk, Ep. 4, 2001 August 21 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - "Lust For Life," Third Watch Bug Music / Virgin, 2001 July (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - "Lust For Life," Best Beer Songs in the World Ever, Vol. 3, New Zealand (v), 2001 July 31 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - "Lust For Life," Ultimate Rock, 2001 November 27 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - "Lust For Life," Arrow Classic Rock Presents: 40 Classic Rock Tracks, 2001 November 29 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - "Passenger," CESPA, Spain advertiser, 2001 Novmeber 28 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - "Hollywood Affair," Hollywood Goes Wild, Virgin, 2001 September 27 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - "Passenger," Absolute Rock Classics, 2001 September 26 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - "Louie Louie," Cover Hits CD, Virgin, 2001 September 26 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - "Search and Destroy," Red Hot Chili Peppers DVD, Bug Music, 2001 September 25 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - "Lust For Life," NBC, Third Watch, 2001 July 26 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - "Passenger," Burning Annie, 2001 December 17 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - "Passenger," Swedish movie, EMI / Solo, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Bass, Gary, Chop Chop film synopsis, 2001 October 15 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Anthill Trading 2001 statement, 2001 December 14 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Controversy Films, Real Kids, 2001 December 7 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Bug Music, Gaumont, 2001 December 7 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - NASCAR, Sig Sigworth, 2001 November 7 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - European Tour 2001, final report 2, 2001 September 27 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - "Lust For Life," VH1 All Access: Commercialism in Music, 2001 June (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - "I Need Somebody," Queer As Folk, 2001 June 27 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - "Passenger," Party Explosion, Sweden, 2001 June 26 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - "Avenue B," Music is the Night, EMI Korea, 2001 July 13 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - "Bad Boyz," BET use, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - "Lust For Life," Kelloggs Vive cereal, 2001 May 25 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Swedish TV, Greatest Pleasure of Life, "Lust For Life", 2001 May 29 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - "Lust For Life," Behind the Music 3rd Anniversary, 2001 May 24 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - "Passenger," Walking Life, Bug Music, 2001 July 9 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - "Lust For Life," Mitsubishi CD, Virgin, 2001 July 18 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Wolff, Petra, letter, 2001 December 1 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Detroit Experiment, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Smith, Steve, Da Mob, FOX TV, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - European tour final report 1, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Solo Reports to Grumble Corporation, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - U.S. tour [RESTRICTED], 2001 October (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - "Candy," EMI Australia, 1990 Where Were You?, 2001 July 17 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - "Lust For Life," "Passenger," HMV box set UK, 2001 July 17 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Real Wild Child, Out of the Box, 2001 July 16 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - L'Espresso, Lust For Life, 2001 April 16 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - "Lust For Life," De Tudloze 100, Volume 5, Belgium, 2001 November 12 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - "Death is Certain," "Talking Snake," "Beat Em Up", Crossing Jordan, 2001-2002 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - "China Girl," Rock and Roll Jeopardy, 2001 November 14 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - "Passenger," Ultimate 70s, 2001 November 20 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - "Lust For Life," Flash Hits, Greece, 2001 November 2 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - "Sixteen," German compilation, 2001 November 27 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - "Passenger," 156 Tricks (surf / skate), 2001 November 28 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - "Lust For Life," Gilmore Girls, Bug Music, 2001 November (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - "Avenue B," Hottracks in Autumn, Korean compilation, 2001 October 31 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - TV's Greatest Moments, Dinah Shore, 2001 October 18 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - "Wild America," Big Day Out 2000 - Disrespective CD, 2001 October 23 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - "I'll Be Seeing You," Listen to This Picture, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Iggy Pop - Ultimate Collection, Hip-O Records, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - "I'm Bored," Molson Dry Bug Music / Quebec, 2001 October 29 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Royal Caribbean amendment / option, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - "Lust For Life," Nikki #226169, 2001 July 2001 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - 2001 Calendars / Bug Music statements, July 2001-September 2001, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 61-62)
  - Bug Music statement, 2001 October-2001 December (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Bug Music royalty statements, 2001 July-2001 September (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Bug Music statements, 2001 October-2001 December (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Old Grey Whistle Test DVD letter, 2001 August 17 (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Hendrix, Jimi, house for sale, eBay, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - Grammy's Art of Music, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Virgin Atlantic, July 2001 (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - Fitzgerald, Jim, book agent, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - Talvitie, Ted, puppet maker, 2001 May 29 (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - Stuff Magazine Nina Alu release, 2001 July 11 (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - Detroit Pistons ad agency, 2001 August (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - David Letterman thank you note, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - Simon, Nina, Mooseman's mom, 2001 August 12 (Box 10, Folder 75)
  - Mid-summer promo, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 76)
  - Fall tour promo requests, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - Arista royalties (and other song licensing), 1994, 1997-2000 (Box 10, Folder 78)
  - Porn-O-Rock, Larry Flynt Publication film, 2001 September 25 (Box 10, Folder 79)
  - Soundscan reports, Beat 'Em Up, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 80)
  - Kamhi, Randi, deposition (Kamhi v. Anisfeld), 2001 (Box 10, Folder 81-82)
  - Bug Music statements, 2001 April-2001 June (Box 10, Folder 83)
  - Virgin promo domestic, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 84)
  - Playbook news magazine, Iggy cover, 2001 October 19 (Box OS1, Folder 1)